anthropologie.eu 2017-06-08

# Privacy & Security Policy

Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us. Our Privacy & Security Policy outlines the information we collect about you, how we use, disclose and otherwise manage this information and the choices you have to restrict our usage of this information.

## Collected Information

We collect personal information when you sign up for anthro, our loyalty program, or to our email updates; or contact us with a comment, question or complaint. This may include, for example, your name, date of birth, email address, postal address, telephone number, whether you are male or female and your product preferences.

## Our Email List

When you sign-up to receive our email updates, we may collect optional information such as your name, post code, and product interests. We use this personal information to tailor our email messages and to enhance our product and service offerings.

## Customer Service

When you contact us with a question, feedback or other comment, you may be asked for information that identifies you, such as your name, address and telephone number. We collect this information to verify your identity and to help us promptly answer your question or respond to your comment or feedback. We may retain this information to assist you in the future. We may also use your feedback, suggestions and comments to monitor and/or improve our products or website.

## Website Information Collected

You can visit our site (anthropologie.eu) without telling us who you are or providing us with any personal information. However, we collect the I.P. (Internet protocol) addresses of all our website visitors and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our website. We use this information to monitor and improve our website.

We use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you access or visit. Cookies are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer so we can recognise you when you return. We use cookies to better understand your use of our website so that we may continue to refine and improve the website. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to disable them. However, if you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features on our website. The information collected through cookies may be combined with other identifiable personal information (such as demographic information) from our records and other sources. We may use this combined information for future marketing initiatives and to help us improve our website presentation.

## Information We Share

We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to other members of the Anthropologie corporate family and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. We may use service providers to process data, host our website, and send emails, in order to help us better understand your use of our website and refine and improve our website. These companies may store and process this information in the United Kingdom or United States.

All of our service providers are required to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information and to use it only in compliance with applicable privacy laws. These companies are not authorised to use your information in any manner, other than in helping us to provide you with products and services or as otherwise required by applicable law.

At various times we may also ask you whether you would be happy for your personal information to be shared with other companies which are not associated with the Anthropologie corporate family. If you agree to this, our Privacy & Security Policy will not apply to their use of your personal information and their own policies will apply.

We may also disclose specific personal information about you if required by law, governmental request or court order if, based on our good faith belief, it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order.

## Sale of Business

Anthropologie may transfer any information we have about you in the event of a merger with a third party or upon a sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party acquirer.

### Retention of Personal Information

We only keep your personal information as long as necessary for the purposes we collected it, or as otherwise required by law.

### Security and Personal Information

Your privacy is important to us. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against the loss, theft, unauthorised access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. We have implemented measures in an effort to safeguard the personal information in our custody and control, including only providing access to personal information to employees and authorised service providers who require such information for the purposes described in this Privacy & Security Policy.

To provide you with an increased level of security, online access to certain personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication.

## Policy Changes

We may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. We will treat your personal information in accordance with the Privacy & Security Policy in place at the time your information was collected.

This Privacy & Security Policy was updated on 10th September, 2010 to take account of your ability to agree to us sharing your personal information with other companies which are not associated with the Anthropologie corporate family.

## Contact Us

Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy or the manner in which we treat your personal information or to withdraw your name from an email or other marketing list.

If you wish to access or update the personal information we have about you, or to correct factual errors in our records, please email us or write to us at the address below. To protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**ANTHROPOLOGIE CUSTOMER SERVICES**

24 WEST STREET

LONDON

WC2H 9NA

Anthropologie is a trading name of URBN UK Limited, a U.K. registered company (company number 03124253 and VAT number 684936382), whose registered office address is: 1 Finsbury Circus, London, EC2M 7SH

## Anthro Loyalty Program

If you have joined our anthro program, based on your mailing preferences, you will receive our catalogue as well as email updates from us that will include advanced notice of sales and promotions, new merchandise, store openings and other news that we think you'll enjoy.

Addresses provided to us are only used internally for the purpose of sending you communication from us. We respect your privacy rights and will not sell or rent your postal or email addresses to other companies.

Anthro members are entitled to free U.K. standard delivery on orders over £75. To activate, log into Anthro account and enter code at checkout. For all future orders, the promotion will be automatically applied at checkout when logged in. Excludes furniture and found items. Not available with any other offer or promotion.

If you would like to unsubscribe from our anthro program, please email [customerservice@anthropologie.eu](mailto:customerservice@anthropologie.eu) or call [00800-0026-8476](tel:0080000268476). You may also click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. We will remove your name from our lists as soon as possible. Please recognise that you may receive another catalogue or email before we are able to remove you.

## Promotional Codes

Unless otherwise expressly stated in the terms and conditions for a particular promotional code, promotional codes cannot be combined and cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer/discount. For example, unless expressly permitted for a particular promotional code, you cannot use a student discount in combination with another promotional code. If you have more than one promotional code and the codes cannot be combined, it is up to you to use the promotional code that has the biggest benefit to you.
